♪ In a not too distant future ♪
♪ It went down in Deep 13 ♪
♪ Dr. Forrester and TV's Frank ♪
♪ They were hatching
an evil scheme ♪
♪ They hired a temp
by the name of Mike ♪
♪ Just a regular Joe
they didn't like ♪
♪ Their experiment
needed a good test case ♪
♪ So they conked
him on the noggin ♪
♪ And they shot him into space ♪
♪ Get me down ♪
♪ For some of them
cheesy movies ♪
♪ The worst we can find ♪
♪ You'll have to sit
and watch them all ♪
♪ And we'll monitor his mind ♪
♪ Now keep in mind
Mike can't control ♪
♪ Where the movies
begin or end ♪
♪ He can try to
keep his sanity ♪
♪ With the help of
his robot friends ♪
♪ Robot roll call Cambot ♪
♪ Gypsy ♪
♪ Tom Servo ♪
♪ Croooow ♪
♪ If you're wondering how
he eats and breathes ♪
♪ And other science facts ♪
♪ Just repeat to yourself
it's just a show ♪
♪ I should really just relax ♪
♪ For mystery science
theater 3000 ♪
- Hi everyone, Mike Nelson
here along with Crow and Servo
aboard the satellite of love.
I thought we'd start
things a little differently
and why don't you join
us as each in our own way
we observe a moment of silence.
- God, this is great, hey!
This is so spiritual I just
can't believe it (laughs)
You know what this
silence thing is like?
Well, I'll tell ya.
I feel like one of them trapper
monks or something (laughs)
No kidding, really.
I feel so purified, O my soul
is as smooth as a
baby's behind (laughs)
and I'm not just talking
insides here, no sir!
I'm talking visions, I'm
talking full blown illumination.
I'm talking about revelation,
shout it down from
the mountain top.
I'm talking huge deafening
thunder clap, the truth.
We'll be under
silence here friends,
we're in the mega-silence.
You heard about the big
bang theory of silence?
This is it man, kaboom! (laughs)
Boy is it quiet.
Wowwee, is it silence or what?
I feel enlightenment,
it's sartory.
It's like I'm sitting
under the body tree, wow!
Wow, that was some round
of silence, hey gents.
- Yeah!
- Well hey, it doesn't
have to end now.
Heck I could be standing
like this all day.
- Oh, you can't!
'cause Mike Johnson and
Todd Langnes are calling.
- Who's that?
- I went to grade
school with them.
- Well, how the hell are we
supposed to know the people
you went to gra--
What do you think, we
carry a yearbook around?
(doorbell rings)
- Just a minute Mike.
Our Chinese food!
- Our Chinese food!
- Here, keep the dime,
you did a great job.
- Okay, let's see here.
Hope they didn't forget
my tangerine chicken.
Nope, here it is.
And my chicken with broccoli.
My chicken with baby corn.
My chicken with peanuts.
My chicken in a
distinctive sauce.
My chicken in sweet and
sour sauce with lemon grass.
- Where is my McDuck?
I'm kidding.
Here, why don't you
send some of these stuff
up to the satellite of love?
Okay?
- Okay!
- Oh wait, wait,
wait, wait, wait!
This!
I'm going to eat my fortune
cookie first (laughs)
I'm so naughty.
You have been summoned to
a place beyond this earth,
a place beyond
your understanding,
a place filled with
laughter and love,
safety and happiness
for all eternity.
A trusted friend
will accompany you
to this other plane of existence
and your journey will begin.
Watch for the signs my friend.
Godspeed and good luck!
What a crappy fortune!
Clay, open yours.
- You will die alone and afraid
knowing not a single human
being ever loved you.
Lucky numbers three, 18 and--
it's weird, I keep
getting the same one.
What about you Nelson?
Have you gotten your order?
- Yeah I believe so.
Crow you've got your romain man?
- Well actually, it's the
death of a salesman special,
and that came with
a really low main.
(slurps loudly)
- Well, no matter.
I'm just gonna enjoy
my hot and sour seafood
and giant clam soup.
Just a cracker in there.
Oh, what the--
Okay, come on, come on.
Whoa, ow!
- (laughs) you kids with
your weird Chinese foods.
Just give me a good ol'
American hotdog any day.
Ho, no, no, no!
Stop it (laughs)
- Okay Frank.
I've got the napkins
and the beverages,
we can start eating.
Well Mike, your movie this week
is a tasty fried dumpling
called Samson versus
the vampire women.
And it's served with a
tangy hot and sour sauce.
Mike, did you leave me any food?
- There's plenty of soy sauce.
- Oh, thank you!
I don't want any soy sauce.
- Give me that goose!
Give me that food you--
oh we got movie time!
(sinister laughter)
- Oh, capital critters is on.
- Why do they have the
blue mask as their symbol?
- Okay granted, he's
the silver maskman,
he didn't need to tell us that.
- Samson the silver
maskman to tag Leana.
- And Delta Burke as Delilah,
aka the silver maskman
versus the vampire women.
- A lighthearted romp about
the war between the sexes.
- Samson versus
the vampire women,
a major Supreme Court case.
- You know, suddenly
I'm in the mood
for a Black Castle hamburger.
- And directed by Joel Smith.
- Remember there
are vampire women,
so get ready with
the Cher jokes.
- Isn't this the castle from
the bottom of a fish bowl?
- What you call hell,
Ramos calls photography.
- We gratefully
acknowledge the cooperation
of the Churubusco-Azteca
film board.
With special assistance
by G. Gordon Liddey.
I dreamed I visited the
El Mandalay last night.
♪ Yes the movie sucks Fernando ♪
- [Crow And Servo] Fabian, ah!
- For the rest of this movie,
everybody is just modest rent.
- You know I went to school
with an Alfonso Corona Blake.
No wait, that was Todd
Langnes I'm sorry.
Owls, imitating a spider monkey.
- Well, I think this
house is ready to show.
- Must be the maid-century off.
- Oh, they keep the
vase nice and polished.
- Yep, one of Newt's
orphanages here.
(hoots owl-like)
- I'll be back Alfred!
- Hey, it's Cobb.
- Looks like Miss
Haversham's summer place.
- Suzanne Pleshette!
Look at how strange her
eyes don't follow you
no matter where you
are in the room?
- Established 1761!
(loud screams)
- Someone taped over Seinfeld.
- Surprise!
♪ Happy birthday to you ♪
- Fang, are you out there?
- Oh, it's Ginger Rogers.
- Lady (laughs)
I guess we caught you
at a bad time, lady.
- Let the Cher jokes, begin.
- Hey, it looks
like Cher (laughs)
- I don't tan.
- Did I release the alarm?
- Ah, the place hasn't changed.
- Oh, I'm the
first one up again.
So I'll make breakfast.
- She's so thin, I hate her.
- This would be a
good place to come
if you were moving
and needed boxes.
- By wamo!
Where did I put my pantyhose?
- Boy, Angie Dickinson
has hit a rough spot.
- She's dressed like
Jeremiah Johnson.
♪ Oh what a beautiful morning ♪
- This place needs a plant.
- This is back when glam
rock was really big.
Can they keep this pace up?
- Alright marines,
grab your socks
and drop your socks.
- You overslept.
- Queen and mistress
of the night,
lady of darkness and mentor
of the vampire women,
you have rested 200 years now.
- This is not a
hotel young lady.
- You've slumbered for
centuries just as you are.
Your master has not
summoned you until now.
The hour is here at last.
You are to make the prophecies
he laid out come true.
He reigns in the dark dominion.
He, your lordly husband
calls your sovereign.
- Just one more century!
- All men are
addicted to corruption
and obligated to seek
self destruction.
- Hey, what--
well, that's true actually.
- They have committed us all,
to awaken and to
call up on monsters
that reside on this earth.
- Would you shut up?
Some people gotta
work in the morning.
- Lay nails.
- You know, I know this
isn't right to say,
but this is an ugly sorority.
- Chinese fire drill.
- I don't mind if
their hair is long,
as long as it's combed neat.
- With Platformate!
- I call the bathroom first.
- Eczema support group
meets in the basement.
- Oh, maybe a
humidifier would help.
- Sorina!
Honor this gathering
of the vampire women.
At last the moment has arrived
when we must select
your successor,
so that you will be free again,
to return to the great
depths of the earth.
To occupy your
throne at his side.
- First the minutes
from the last meeting.
- To all mortalize, a queen
of the most radiant beauty,
because you are destined
to scourge and seduce men.
- Well, wake that
lady up, come on!
- And you as well
my sisters, I call
- No tag backs.
- I Tundra!
The one selected to
order and guide you
as priestess of vampires.
I must carry out my mission.
Hold, I will see that you are
nourished with human blood.
- I have a question.
- He is here, listen to our cry
O inscrutable Lord of darkness.
- I'm doing it.
- Imponderable king of
witchcraft and black magic.
Protect us under
your great powers.
- Okay!
- Render us invulnerable
to the assaults
and attack of mortals.
- Anything else?
- Shield our bodies and our
eyes from the sign of the cross,
and help us to avoid daylight.
- No daylight, yeah of course.
- Our worst enemy is the sun.
- Hold on, let me
right this all down.
- Don't make us touch
fire that purifies all.
- [All Vampires] Let this be
your will O lord of darkness.
- Yes, oh sorry!
Stepped on the plug there.
- The devil doesn't like me.
- A shark!
- Some of them went
on to start whole.
♪ Rihanna ♪
(upbeat music)
- Salin hear my cry.
- V-I-C-T-O-R-Y
- Let your immortal
rays touch us.
Give me the appearance
that I'll need now.
I must have beauty in order
to fulfill my mission.
- I think she looks good now.
- You are the breath that
gives life to my body.
- Quit kissing up.
- You are my spirit,
and awaken your
sleeping slaves as well.
- Mexico really needs
a Martha Stewart.
- My servants!
- Hey, pretty good for a strike.
- Another successful
Jose A Bahr makeover.
- I'm pretty, so
I have value now.
- She has to hold her arms
up till her roll on dries.
- They got some
pretty busy spiders
in this era horror movies.
- Ah yes, the three
Russian aviators.
- Salin hear my cry.
(mimicked cries)
And awaken your slaves.
- Salin, I believe I asked
you nicely to hear my cry.
- And you the dead.
- The dead, whoo!
- The dead, book of magnolia.
- Awaken from the sleep
that has kept you silent
for 200 years.
- Silent except for Ted.
Boy was he sawing logs.
- Tim Allen!
- So for 200 years, nobody
tried to develop this castle
into upscale town homes?
- Oh, must not have
worn his headgear.
- A Jacky Mason.
- What am I doing here,
why am I in a castle?
Why am I in a crypt?
I'm a vampire.
- Huh jeez!
I've been awake since 1890.
- It just come undone, he
could have left anytime.
- I like me.
- This guy's change is
a little more subtle.
- They've given him
better heart support.
- Skipper!
- It's the pips!
- (sniffs) Do I smell bacon?
- Follow me.
- Looks like a Stuart
Anderson's cattle company.
- Uh, just do what
she does I guess!
- Boy I'd be nervous sleeping
under that chandelier.
There's no railing
here so look out.
- Did you ever see
a Polish magnet?
Here, it's over this way.
- Which one is Brad Pitt?
(owl hoots loudly)
- I took a wrong turn.
- Oh, I know!
She woke 'em up so that
they can move the couch.
- Don't I look fat
in that picture.
- Look at her!
200 years ago,
she was selected by the
king of the dark dominions
to succeed our great Sorina.
It was your fault that she fled
from the hand of
my sister vampires.
- We're confused.
- Yes, at that time
an extraordinary girl,
dedicated to a life of virtue
caused us to fail
in our sacred duty.
- I'm a crappy vampire.
- Her beauty and
kindness were handed down
to a descendant of hers.
And so tonight you
will all see her.
When she has reached her
21st year we must capture her
so that she'll be here to
take part in our great ritual.
- Now let's get out there
and take it to 'em
in the second half.
- Remember if you
fail this time,
- It's hard for
women to be managers.
- I have great power
and I will destroy you.
You'll be converted
into dust, understand?
- We swear we will not
fail you again Tundra.
- That's permafrost
to you mister!
- Sorina needs blood and my
sisters and I need it also.
She needs young blood.
- Eek (laughs)
- That is our job tonight.
Follow me, we'll
search for human blood.
- I say we start by
searching for humans.
- Oh wait, my string is tangled.
Ow, look out.
- They were gonna have vampires
take the form of squirrels
but it wasn't the same.
- So she was Nora
Dunn 200 years ago?
(gentle piano music)
♪ As time goes on ♪
♪ I dedicate this
song to thorazine ♪
♪ And boy, boy, boy, boy ♪
- She's auditioning
for Freddy de Cordova.
- What we call a second
and third movement.
- Remember when we had to
listen to a stand-up act?
(mumbles) a little tight but
I think I can get through it.
- I'm gonna break into
some heavy blues now here.
- No, no, no, you naughty
boy, don't look at me.
- Now Dean Martin's gonna
come in and jump on the piano.
- Hey, the woodland
creatures love her music.
- I don't get the physics
of a hovering bat.
- New vampire position
flight team in formation.
I don't know how long
I can keep this up.
Wait, wait!
There's the note
I like, yeah, aha!
- We'll go wait in that car,
just wanted to
fly over with you,
make sure you got here safe.
- Finger in this appalling,
and the freezing is
confused and messy.
- I'm really wasted.
The Mexican Larry
Tate, El Stevens.
- Loan me your sweater.
I want to loan her my sweater
and I don't need it back.
- Just like Count
Basie, one more time.
- Beethoven from the grave
renounces his great work.
- Ay great!
You know that
thing from peanuts?
- I'm blitzed and I
don't care who knows it.
- General Hospital.
- She's charging, look out!
- I'm sorry you couldn't
get a better seat,
but we're sold out.
Shkout!
- If bats got into his hair,
they'd drown in the Vaseline.
- But the bats
liked your playing,
they were very supportive.
- Hang on Diana,
what happened to you?
- I don't know George,
but it all was so strange.
All of a sudden I heard
a voice calling me
from a tremendous distance.
- Saying drink more gin.
- There wasn't
anything out there.
Could have been a bird.
I think, I saw something fly.
- It's most likely that
you're nervous Diana.
You know I bet it was
a butterfly out there
attracted to the
light and that's all.
- Alright, Tony Candor,
waiting for you to die.
- I guess you're right,
it was only my nerves.
George dear, you know
tomorrow we announce
our wedding plans
during the party.
- We do?
- And tomorrow's my birthday.
- Right, and now that you're
feeling better darling,
remember we're going out.
- But George, I'd prefer that
Diana stay here in
the house tonight.
- Why professor?
- I don't know really,
but she's fatigued
and better rest tonight.
- Papa's telling the truth dear.
I'm a little tired and I
prefer to go to bed early.
And tomorrow I'll feel
much better George.
Is that okay?
- Alright then you win.
Anyway, pretty soon
you'll be using my name
and I'll give the
orders around the house.
- You will be my slave.
- Don't you agree professor?
- Oh yes, certainly of course.
- Goodnight George.
- Tomorrow you'll feel better.
- Oh the passion.
- I'm going up papa.
- Get a good rest darling.
- Oh wait, when did
you get that tattoo?
Now you get back here,
don't you ignore me.
Well, goodnight.
- Professor
- Your daughter's hot.
- I know something
is worrying you.
You're trying to hide it.
- No, no, it's nothing.
The trouble is that you're
a little nervous also.
You are imagining things.
- Well I don't know,
you seem to be acting
pretty strange tonight.
- Yeah but, it's so funny
that you would think that.
Just because you say
I'm acting strange,
I don't sound like.
- Sorry, but I don't
agree with you.
- That guy has a
funny voice (laughs)
- You are not going to
be losing a daughter.
On the contrary, you'll
be gaining a son.
- Come on Mike, how
do you play this game?
- Well, it's pretty easy,
you just move a piece
and you go, stratego!
- Oh, I think I can do that.
Move a piece there, stratego!
- Oh I get it.
Hey, hey look you
guys, look, look!
- Sure Crow,
anything to win hey?
- Come on, were right in the
middle of a game here, come on.
Stratego!
- But he's right there.
He's right there, I
think it's a star child.
Hey he's--
What?
Really?
When?
Oh I see!
Yes!
Yes, of course!
It all makes sense now.
- Stratego!
- Alright Crow, your turn.
- Something's going
to happen Mike.
Something wonderful.
I know I'm about
to win (laughs).
Stratego!
- Hey.
(upbeat music)
- Uh huh, that's right Crow.
- How are you George?
- I'm not sure you
understand that game.
- Hello Charles.
- Tell me Inspector, you're
working on an investigation
or stopping a crime?
- I just came to say hello
to my dear old friend
Professor Rollof,
and to say that
since Diana's
starting a new life,
we can play chess
every night now.
- But you're coming to the
masquerade ball, aren't you?
- Yes, I guess so.
I'll be coming as
Sherlock Holmes.
Although I haven't received
my invitation as yet,
unfortunately!
- But that's why I asked
you to come tonight.
I wanted to give you the
invitation in person, Inspector.
- Let me go write it quick.
- Well I'll say goodnight.
See you tomorrow Inspector!
- Goodbye for now George.
- See you tomorrow Professor!
- Sleep well George.
- Some butlers stay inside sir.
- Shut up and get outside.
- Yes sir!
- Please come into the
private study Charlie.
- What was that all about?
- Please walk through the door
into the private study Charlie.
- He's got a picture of
Reddy Kilowatt up over there.
- I'm very shy
around inspectors.
- Now why all they mystery?
I can see that you are
anxious to speak to me.
- I am not anxious, it
is you who are anxious.
- You see, Diana is
in terrible danger,
but what's a good way
to explain it to you.
- Puppet theater?
- Well that's easy,
start by explaining.
- I can't Charles.
I'm at a loss.
- Be frank, I want to
hear all the details.
I am to understand that Diana
could be in danger, Professor.
I've been summoned here,
because you hope I'll find an
adequate way to protect her,
isn't that true?
And nevertheless, you
can't or won't tell me
what is happening.
- And that makes it hard
to get the scene going.
- How can you expect any help
when I don't know who it is
I must protect
you daughter from.
- Charles, I'm usually quite
direct and I don't like secrets
but in this case,
I hesitate now,
because you see
I'm not sure yet,
that's about what you'll say.
- Someone is trying
to kidnap Diana
so they can collect
ransom from you.
Come on now, speak up.
- No, no, I swear
it's not true Charles.
No, it's something far more
terrible than death itself,
it's horrifying, I'm at a loss.
- But forget I said anything.
- That's all I'm
going to tell you now.
Should you decide
to help me, fine.
If not, then leave me alone.
- Look, you invited me here.
- Now, take it easy Professor.
I'll help you and
willingly, but how?
- I can't tell you,
now leave me alone.
- Tomorrow night, I'd like you
to gather together some men
and good men, and come
to the party Charles.
I mean to protect Diana.
- Now get out of here.
- Now look, if she's in danger
why not suspend the party?
- That's impossible!
Diana's very sentimental.
It's only what
the girl deserves,
but at the same time she
can't know the facts either.
My, the situation
is desperate now.
- But Professor, let me
know what's happening here.
Simply for Diana's good.
- No, don't insist.
I repeat I can't
say anymore Charles.
Now do me a favor,
leave me alone.
I have work to get done tonight.
- Be sure to stop
by again tomorrow,
and then leave immediately.
- No wait, come back.
- Why won't he help me.
- Please shut the film
off and discuss now.
What would you have done to
make this a better party?
If only I had a television set.
- Hey, he's a CB owner!
- I wonder what his handle is.
- Better review the
wriggles of etiquette again.
- Consult my sacred
roll of brawny.
- They let Billy draw
today's pamphlet.
- At the end of 200 years,
- I'll tell him something.
- Tundra will seek revenge
on one of Rebeca's descendants.
This unfortunate young girl,
will inherit the beauty
that her ancestor enjoyed.
And when she becomes
21 years of age,
she will be initiated
into the black rituals
of the vampire women
to succeed Sorina.
- Page two!
- On her left shoulder,
she will carry the
figure of a vampire,
the unmistakeable sign
of her tragic destiny.
- Her tragic destiny was
announced by her parents
of Red Wing, Minnesota.
- I looked better before
I tried to look good.
- Ow, ow, ow, ow!
- It's butterfield ocho.
- Now when was I a
flying leather neck?
- Bothered by
unsightly demon marks?
- I shouldn't have
gotten drunk at Sturgess.
- I'm responding to your
let's get acquainted ad.
(loud screams)
- I suppose I have to read her
the very hungry
caterpillar again.
- I gotta have this
room soundproofed.
(spooky haunting music)
- Huh, Garth Hudgen's outside.
- Diana, what happened?
- But I can't stay
long, so don't tell me.
- (sobs) saw the face
behind the window.
It was visibly hideous papa!
So dead and ugly!
- Don't talk about
your mother that way.
- And so diabolical, it
seemed to be spying on me
through the window.
- Mind if I throw that
butterfly theory at you again?
- Calm down darling!
Calm down!
You didn't see anything,
you're only nervous.
You're imagining things.
- No!
I can't forget that
incident downstairs,
when I was sitting at the piano.
And then this horrible face
is not in my imagination dad.
This is all real.
I know, but I can't find
an explanation for it.
- Funny!
- But I know that it
exists, and I'm afraid dad.
- You're getting
pons on my suit.
- Come on sweetheart,
please calm down.
I repeat, you
didn't see anything,
have faith in your father.
- You're probably just crazy.
- And this thing
it has a meaning,
I was born with this
and you know it.
- Your arm, yes it's true.
- And how I've always
wanted to know what it meant
and always you refuse
to tell me dad.
Now, what is it?
Isn't it strange it should
be shaped like a vampire?
- It's only a mark
like any other darling.
I've seen plenty
on other persons.
Not the same as yours, I know,
but they had some strange shape
and they didn't mean a thing.
Why not have faith
in your dad darling?
- These other persons were
all cast into hell of course.
- Tell me Diana, just where
did you see this thing,
this ugly and horrible
face in the night?
- I saw it in the mirror,
when I was combing my hair dad.
- In the mirror, you see?
Didn't you ever read that
light does curious things
when it bounces off a mirror?
It reproduces
figures and shadows.
I've been fooled like
that many times dear.
Why should I try to kid
you it's not logical.
Come dear, cry and
get some sleep now.
Should you need me,
I'll be in the study.
And there's no need
to worry any longer.
- Many times lint
gets in your eye
and takes on ghoulish shapes,
it happens to everyone.
- Well, better get
some Holy Water,
gonna need a cross, some
garlic, maybe some saw,
a demon I can't believe it.
- That mirror thing
was pure genius.
- I gotta get a better fan.
(upbeat music)
I'll send for your
car Mr. Lagose.
- Thank you sir!
- We had a really
Hispanic time, thank you.
- The entire Mexican middle
class ladies and gentlemen.
(laughter)
- So the devil's
minions are cheap thugs.
- Over the lips and
through the gum,
look out stomach, here it comes.
(loud whistle shrill)
- Hey, I've got a
load of vampires here.
- They didn't count on
Carlton the doorman.
- It's a vampire wilding.
Tell your friends the
vampires are here.
- I need more eyeliner.
- Yes, they're real.
- Now that's great puppetry.
- Trying to catch flies?
- These two blue marks close
together on the victim's neck,
are what have me
puzzled Inspector.
Besides that we didn't find one
drop of blood in the corpse.
Why you could swear that a
vampire murdered the girl.
- Hey, now that
I think about it,
I'll bet those monsters
were vampires Doc.
And right after she
attacked the girl,
she changed into a vampire.
She sucked her blood and
then she began to change.
- Take him along boys and put
him under a week's detention.
- But listen chief, listen
I'm not crazy I tell you.
It's true I tell you, it's true.
Those were vampires that I saw.
- You said the same thing about
a parking violation yesterday.
- Are there any internal
injuries doctor?
- No, I'm fine!
- No, none Inspector!
- And those two
blue holes there,
don't you really
know what they are?
- No I don't!
I can tell you one thing
and there's no mistake
about it my friend.
- I'm Coco Chanel
- I attribute these two holes
to some strange animal
whose species is unknown,
and there's no way that
I can determine it.
- Well, I think
it was the vampire
but let's keep
that guy locked up.
- You seem disappointed, I
should have made up an answer.
- That's it!
- Ah, the rainforest cafe.
- They're gonna wax
his bikini area.
- The torture of Don Defour.
- Now what do you know
about the doorman industry?
- They're worshiping
a giant Toblerone.
- It's a Mandrel sisters
Halloween special.
- Now, who said I'm a mascot?
- I thought liturgical
dance was dead!
- Do we have an agenda Susan?
- Would you just get
out of the coffin?
Dive in girls, the
buffet is open.
- Oh you got a little,
let me get, little...
- I'd like to thank the academy.
- Sorina, queen of
the vampire women,
- Here.
- The hour for you to acquire
your original
beauty has arrived.
- I've learned to appreciate
my off-beat looks.
- She's got combination skin.
One part is fetted and
one part is rotted.
- Ladies and gentlemen,
Miss Putresence.
- She looks like a
magic eye picture.
♪ Woke up ♪
♪ Get out of bed ♪
♪ Dragged a comb
across my head ♪
- I'm so sure Debbie
gets to be queen
when she's been asleep
for five centuries.
I mean like I work the
float and everything.
- She thinks she's hot
snot on a silver platter
but she's just a cold
booger on a paper plate.
- She's just Princess
Kay of the Yucky Way.
Hey, how's the snake hangin'?
Go play with your ball.
- Who didn't use a coaster?
Oh, she's a member
of the mug club.
- I swear I'll just
nurse this one.
- Ah, I was gonna
ask you something
but I can't remember now.
- Rise, the presence of his
pants prove there is a God.
- The making of the
international mail catalog.
- You know it's hotter
than hell in here.
- I wonder if this is
considered a sweet assignment
for those guys.
- You want a sip?
- I ordered a Tom Collins.
- Don't gob in it.
- Salin, hear my cry.
This is the moment!
This is the moment to carry
out the supreme sacrifice.
We must have blood
and he is ready to die.
- I am?
What wait...
- We're out of
blood, is Pepsi okay?
- Too much middle management
in this organization.
- Can I get a softer slab?
- Oh sir, I implore
you to close your legs.
- Tab's got sass.
- I just came in for a cleaning.
- Oh bite me!
- Demi Moore, Michael
Douglas, Disclosure.
- Once you let yourself
go, it feels kinda good.
- Body by Jake!
- Alright, O negative
on tap, whoo!
- Hey, somebody tip him
up so we get all of it.
- Put us in coach, come on.
- This is what Southern Baptists
think Catholic Mass is like.
- Who wants blood?
- [Crow And Servo] I do, I do.
- So once you drain the blood,
can they just dump
it in the driveway?
- No, they're gonna take it
to the garage and then...
- I wonder if there are
vegetarian vampires.
- No, you can't donate
again for a week.
- Can you imagine the huge
apocalyptic grease fire,
if they threw Rush
Limbaugh in there?
- Oh, he's green, the
fire is all smoky.
- You got me up for that?
He's gonna get you so pretty.
Hey, it's big Ethel.
She's gonna have a great
big blood mouthwash.
Do it, go on, finish it.
- Finish it.
Ah, it must be a Merlot.
- I'm just waiting
for that click Maggie.
Anna Maria Albergetti.
- Satan has given me
prominent cheekbones.
- There are some
happy vampires here.
- She's the Thelma
Ritter of the group.
- You look at this
rocked hard gave me?
- Let them drink, our
sisters are impatient.
- Do you think
drinking will help.
- Oh, that's it?
I was expecting another
order, I'm sorry!
- Here honey, take
an extra big sip.
- Hey, Lily snagged in a cup.
- Well, it doesn't always work.
- Yes, chaday!
♪ Your love is king ♪
- This Joe Cocker here
in the foreground.
- Come on, come on!
I just need a little beauty man!
Just a little bit please!
Just make me a little
bit pretty come on!
(upbeat music)
♪ Singing in the bathtub ♪
♪ Na na ni nana ♪
- Hey, check out the faint
glow emanating from Deep 13.
- Wow!
- What is with all the
ethereal stuff today?
(loud snores)
- Frank!
Frank, awaken my child.
Frank!
- Jesus?
- No!
- Togo!
- Yes, that was the name.
And thus may you still call me.
Though now, I am Togo the White.
Join me Frank of TV
in a beautiful place
where all the lackeys and
toadies and whipping boys
are forever safe and free
from their oppressors.
- Sounds great.
Can Dr. Forrester come?
- No, the point is you
wouldn't want him there.
- Hey, they fixed
your knees, huh?
- There are no bum knees
in my world, child.
- And how about your voice?
- What about my voice?
- Now, arise, TV's
Frank and join me
for they are all here,
Tonto and Kato and Robin
and Don Wilson and Gaby Hayes.
- And Joe Pesca?
- Yes, all of them.
In short, yes, we
have second bananas.
- Wow, so Togo was
ctually working with
two completely
reconstructed knees?
That is dedication, amazing!
- Crow, Frank is gone.
- Well, that's amazing too.
- I think that if
Frank was still here
he would want us to say--
(alarm vibrating)
- We've got movies time.
- That's not what I meant
at all, you monsters.
- Wow!
- You've seen the girl
chosen as my successor?
- Yes majesty!
And likewise, I have
seen on her skin the mark
that identifies her.
- It's a liver spot.
- The dark vampire.
She is truly lovely your queen,
her beauty rivals yours.
- Yeah right!
- She will be a
deserving successor.
Tomorrow's her
birthday, she'll be 21.
And we all know
the prophecy says,
that she is to stand in
your August presence here,
when the ceremony
starts O queen.
- We dropped our contacts.
- (mumbles) I'm to
terminate my reign.
It is written,
that I am to return
to the depths of
the dark dominion.
If you fail me again, my
vengeance will know no limits.
- Hear us O queen
who rules the night,
sovereign of the vampire women.
- And a good friend
- I shall not fail this time
I promise you.
(thunder clap)
- If I could just
interject here (laughs)
we couldn't help overhearing.
- The how and why
book of vampire women.
- Oh, why did I agree to
proof read this Nichner novel?
- Hey, I found a great
thermo, I'm riding an updraft.
- Hi!
- So, she comes,
sucks on your neck,
you live for all
eternity, she's super hot,
what's the problem here.
- Someone is undressing
me with their eyes.
- Miss Tennessee has
wandered away from the home.
- Oh, I see the spanking
service has arrived.
- Tom!
- Transfer the county's
funds to derivatives.
- Anderson windows and wha--
hello!
- She's got a beefy
assistant with a flash light,
crouched in the bushes.
- She just got hard contacts.
- I know I look
like Vincent Price.
- In God's name I
order you to disappear.
Against Him and His
power you're nothing.
- Oh use the G word, no fair.
- Turns out, jeez I don't have
the acceleration I used to.
- Jeez, I'm as mental
as my loony daughter.
- Hi, and at last you got here--
(laughter)
- I came as soon as I got
your message Professor.
What's going on?
- I feel sort of silly
right now, did I overdress?
- I think you'll recall
that for years now,
I've been translating these
crumbling old parchments here.
They belong to my ancestors,
and in which they announce
the tragic destiny
that awaits my daughter Diana.
- Right I remember that.
- No I haven't forgotten.
Tomorrow's the day Professor.
Diana's about to become of age.
Have you found anything
that will help?
An important clue
that could be used
to stop those monsters
when they try to take her?
- I studied it Samson.
But the things I found
out are not encouraging.
And I fear that there's
no hope for her.
- Should I get into my costume?
- Oh, I forgot my bi-focus.
- Here they affirm that
according to the apocalypse,
we're living at a time
when things are perfect
for the resurrection of
monsters here on earth.
Since men are bent on
wrecking destruction
upon the world today,
they'll heed their
selfish desires
and use the tremendous power
that nature has given us.
- Do you need any
wrestling done?
- Yes, nuclear energy.
- But there's something worse
than what I mentioned just now.
- Are his nipples painted on?
- I spoke to you about
that strange and extraordinary
lad who saved Rebecca's life.
The documents say that he
also would have a descendant.
An outstanding young man
of enormous strength,
destined to hide his identity
under a silver-colored
mask, Samson.
That extraordinary young
man is obviously you.
- Oh, obviously!
- But I should tell
you something else.
According to the prophecies,
even you might fail
trying to protect Diana.
- It's a vague prophecy.
- All the evil they can muster
is against you in this thing.
And so you might be killed
attempting to save my daughter.
- Nevertheless I
have to continue.
I have to go on the
way my ancestors did,
to eliminate evil of all kinds.
And human vampires are monsters
that can never expose
themselves to direct daylight.
Surely they use a hideout
of some kind as a refuge.
And there possibly we could
surprise and destroy them.
- I know!
- Still I said...
- It could be that
these symbols here
refer to their hideout.
But in spite of all
my efforts Samson,
I failed trying to decipher
their hidden meaning.
- That's too bad, well
I've got a golf date
with Randy The Macho Man.
- But I'll be ready for
anything, so don't worry.
- Should I follow
you over there or...
- You're coming to the party
to protect Diana, aren't you?
- No Professor, I
have other plans.
- I'll bet!
- But I'll be responsible
for Diana's safety.
- Another man gone.
Is there something about my
study that drives people away?
(ballroom music)
- Mexico is one goofy country.
- I don't know, I just came
home and they were here.
- Any bad puppets?
Nope, no bad puppets.
- Why is he wearing
a waste basket?
- I came dressed as a Mexican.
- They are chaperoning the
hell out of this party.
- This party is out of control.
Tonight we're gonna
party like it's 1959.
- Now don't forget
my instructions.
No one is to enter this
house without an invitation.
- Very well sir.
- Jeeves' final year
as exile to Mexico.
- I'd like to apologize in
advance for our wedding night.
- She was supposed
to come as a bat.
- Looks like the guy
from House Party.
- Oh yeah, it's kid or play.
- She's gonna call
us the undead.
- Are you feeling ill?
- I gorged myself on a cracker.
- Just for a moment
there I was dizzy.
Let's sit down please.
- It's a rockin' party,
what with the Strauss
and the dancing and--
- I never thought I'd
long for a Mariachi band.
- My poor girl's happy.
Just watch her face.
She of course doesn't suspect
that tonight could be
really tragic for her.
- You have an odd way about you.
- Don't worry so much
about her Professor.
Why do you think we're here?
We'll stop any attack
that they could begin.
- Provided the attack is
lame and poorly thought out
and it's our grandmas.
- Mickey Splain locked out
of another society party.
♪ I have often stalked
down this lane before ♪
- So then, I sailed
around Cape Hope
and of course King Ferdinand,
he's a really good
friend of mine,
I can introduce you.
- You killed one of the
Dutch Masters, you fiends!
- Jeez, this one is really hard.
- Ah good, my order's up.
- Well, that's our limit.
- Oh, Giorgio, makes me gag.
- Nope, never lost
a party guest.
- Now hide them.
In a little while,
we'll be back.
- She must have
drank Chinese blood.
- Boy I tell you, you
only rent blood huh?
- Meanwhile, back at the
world's most joyless party.
- Please stop playing the waltz.
- I only wish he was in costume.
- Now do you feel better?
- Now how about now?
Do you feel better now?
What if I do this?
Is this better,
better now, now huh?
How about now?
- You here's my invite.
- A Mister and Miss Vampire
of Passaic New Jersey.
- They're actually gonna
perk up this party.
(waltz music)
- You are not the Kissingers!
- Please excuse
the question but...
- Would you sleep with me?
- Maybelline, fine
makeup, sensibly priced.
- I will get your cream of week.
- Huh, good job Ted,
you were firm but fair.
- Is she okay then?
- I'd say she's hot, hot hot!
- Oh good, they are finally
putting the salmon out.
- She's totally
attracted to my hat.
Hi, wanna look inside my hat?
- Come on over, go ahead
and look at the sweat band.
- I did the glitter myself.
- You home wrecker!
- You know what they say
abut guys with big hats, huh?
- You know once you go
cossack, you never go back.
- Aren't some of the
costumes here weird?
- Yeah!
- Hey, you wanna wrestle?
♪ Ten minutes ago I met you ♪
♪ And we murmured
a how do you do ♪
- I should tell you
that sometime ago,
a prophecy was spoken up.
Oh what the hell, give
me another black Russian.
- I just realized that this
is a totally boring party.
Let's bring out the peyote.
- Prep to her, hurry Inspector!
(loud whistle shrill)
(dogs barking)
(loud screams)
- Alright, make out time.
- This should have
happened hours ago.
The party is finally
coming to life.
- Get that man,
he's getting away.
- Hey Mr. Wayne.
- Uh oh, more
supernatural tomfoolery.
- Wanna buy a watch?
- Don't fire, your
bullets could wound her!
(spooky haunting music)
(loud gun shots)
- Oh, go ahead and fire,
whatever you think.
- They've got the poker queen.
- Oh no!
- Wee, it's fun being the
eternal damned, whoohoo!
Come on skipper.
- He's got the ball
at the 20, the 10,
he could go all the way.
- It's the Santo mobile.
- I can't believe
I forgot my cup.
- Hey, mom said you guys
have to let me play.
- Did we have a plan
for this people?
- The undead
recruits of the WWF.
- Where are the
cocktail weenies?
- Hug pile.
- Oh, titty twister, not fair.
- Stop, not yet, Samson's
fighting against them now.
Wait till they're separated.
- Oh, they separated, that's
too bad, I hadn't noticed.
- Well, now they
gotta call Joan Embry.
- Get the tennis rackets.
- The Malibu getaway car.
- Just leave me
out here, I'm fine.
I'll sleep it, it's
cool out here, please.
- Do you think you
can still shottish?
- Well, tonight you folks
need to turn down the Strauss
a little bit, there's
been some complaints.
- We heard shots
from this direction,
is anything wring Inspector?
- Nothing, nothing!
You can go now.
- Thank you, thank
you, I'll go now.
(car engine growls)
(sirens wailing)
- Chief, I saw two
corpses in the garden.
- Oh, bye!
- Just a moment.
Not a word about
the things you saw
here in the garden tonight.
Or they'll put us in the
booby hatch I'm sure of that.
- That's exactly what
we were thinking.
- Tell the jailers to
free that little officer
that informed us about
that flying vampire.
And call for an ambulance too.
- Right chief!
Come on boys.
- Even after dispatching orders,
I feel empty.
- And that was when I was
captain of the pep squad.
- I never would have believed it
if I hadn't seen it
with my own eyes.
- Now you know why I hesitated
to explain it to you.
- Don't you have
the slightest idea
where to find the hideout
that these creatures
are living in?
(phone rings)
- Ah, that must be one of my
many wrestling acquaintances.
- Oops, pardon my phone.
- Hello!
This is the residence
of Professor Rollof.
Yes!
For you Charles.
- Ah, make it quick, we
got a movie going on, okay?
- Thank you!
Yes!
I'm the Inspector, go ahead.
- No I don't know the
count or the amount.
- Alright!
I'll be there later.
- I have to go home and
empty the dishwasher.
- Another pair was attacked at
the same spot as last night.
They'd been in the
nightclub also.
The poor girl was killed
and they found the same
small holes on her neck.
Her escort was kidnapped.
- They kidnapped her car,
what was the point of that?
- Now that's an idea.
- Put the cheese
inside the cracker.
- The crimes that are committed
there these last two nights,
could furnish us with a clue.
- Copernicus?
- It's evident that
they use that area to attract
their victims in some way.
- Hello, anybody here?
- I think we'll have to play
all our cards this time and--
- Edna, Edna, look!
- [Charles] But tomorrow night
we'll go to that night club
and we'll take Diana with us.
- [Professor] Are you
out of your mind Charles?
- You are a mean one mister!
- Under the circumstances,
Diana is in just
as much danger here
as she would be
in any other area.
Now, don't worry!
I'll send guards to
surround the block
and they won't cause suspicion.
My best trained men are going
to be in that nightclub too.
- Now look what happened out
there in the garden tonight.
And your men's bullets
couldn't detain
those infernal
creatures Charles.
- Yes, but all in
all I don't think
anything's going
to happen to Diana.
And on the other hand,
it's quite possible
that we'll find out
who those monsters are
and that diabolic
female that leads them.
It's a chance but they
could reveal their hideout.
So now please have
confidence in me Professor.
If you don't, you'll
be running a great risk
and you might not save Diana.
- And the risk is...
- The Inspector is right papa!
Sooner or later those
monsters are going to find me.
Why not try this
as a last resort?
Anything is preferable to
continuing this nightmare.
- The plan just might
work too professor.
- You win, I'll
go along with you.
- No Professor, you
should stay here
and wait to hear from Samson.
Now try to get a
little rest Diana.
The house is under
constant guard.
- Now let's get back to
the party and Strauss out.
- Let's get you back to
the Lawrence Welk show.
- I thought we drained him
pretty good, how about you?
- Yeah, we're getting
pretty good at this (laughs)
Let's see, one, two,
watch your kidneys.
Up we go!
A heavy sucker, huh?
- Yeah, so you guys going over
to Steve's after the shift?
- Okay Shelley, truth, dare,
double dare, promise or repeat?
- You have failed me
once again Tundra.
- You kiped my eyeliner.
- There is a terrible
enemy in our way Sorina.
His name is Samson,
and he is to blame.
The girl that was chosen
as your successor,
was in our power when
he got there tonight.
But tomorrow he'll
be dead Sorina.
This I swear in the
name of your husband,
the king of the dark dominion.
- I am watching the game.
- You know I must
terminate my reign soon.
So tomorrow you are to
have my successor here.
My vengeance is
cruel and terrible.
- Phyllis Newman has gone nuts.
- As well your sisters
will be changed to dust.
- That's what happens
if you don't moisturize.
- Alright, there goes
half the bowling team.
- Key ripes!
Fiends are visiting from Europe.
- Give me another opportunity,
I shall not fail again.
- Tundra, I wish to see
my successor tonight.
Take me to her!
- You order and I
obey, sovereign.
- You're damn straight.
(upbeat music)
- You're wanted on
the telephone sir.
- It's Lucy Ricardo, she
wants to be in the show.
(soft foreign music)
- This isn't Strauss.
- Thank you, thank you.
That was (speaks
foreign language)
- Two for the Vikings, I've
got two for the Vikings.
- That Danny DeVito has arrived.
- Why do you suppose
they want the Inspector?
- Well I--
- Aha, indeed, well put!
♪ We will crush the
imperialists running does ♪
- There's always a line
in the ladies' wa--
- I was speaking to
Professor Rollof.
Samson hasn't phoned
and he's worried.
I understand that tonight
he fights at the arena.
So maybe he'll get in touch
with us a little later on.
- This must be the arena, where
Samson is fighting tonight.
Perhaps he'll get in
touch with them later on.
- Oh, they're making the
beats with two butts.
- You know, it
actually looks fun.
- Says you.
They were the inspiration for
the (mumbles) Stance Company.
- The ruling party
set the debate format.
- Oh no!
- Sure they made fun
of him in high school
but just look at him now.
- And now before I have
my match with Samson.
- It's gonna be a
real tough fight.
- I wanna take a little nap.
- Oh, butt crack, look out.
- Make sure you
lock the door Willy,
I don't want nobody
to disturb me.
- He looks like an
executioner on break.
- Mount man, wow!
- Hey, we're out of
toilet paper in here.
- I was sent by fantasy gram.
♪ When a man loves a wrestler ♪
- Oh, someone let me down there.
- Mr. Wrestler, are you
trying to seduce me?
- This scene was cut
out of Spartacus.
- Oh, it's a Robert
Maple farm photo session.
- You have a kind face.
- Come to the dark side or
I'll take your lunch money.
- I'll see you in hell.
- Actually I will,
I'm down there a lot.
- Oh crap, it's the wrong guy.
- Now I better dress him
and tie him onto the fender
and get him home.
- Then there's all the
paperwork down in hell.
- Oh, gee, should have
seen that one coming.
- This is one of the weirder
parts of the Menendez trial.
- I can see why Cyndi
Lauper loves this sport.
- It's NDL Kauffman.
- Why can't they just talk
about whatever's bothering them
instead of this
senseless wrestling?
- Ow, that hurt me.
- You're on now!
- Say, is your body
remarkably different
from when I was just in here?
- It's a little chilly
in the ring tonight.
Take this light wrap,
okay honey?
- There let's go.
- Let's go to our
night at the theater.
- Ding ding, we
need a volunteer.
- Sit down, everybody sit down.
We're not gonna start the match
until everybody sits down.
(crowd chanting and whistling)
- The wrestling program in
hell, is second only to Iowa.
- The second Schmeling-Satan
fight went on for 15 rounds.
(crowd chanting)
- Thank you, thank
you very much.
But I'm just the
referee, thank you.
- Three falls allowed and
there's no time limit tonight.
- Brother!
- We are seeing
the main event of the evening.
- In this corner here, the
black mask, the challenger.
(crowd whistles and jeers)
- Nobody likes me.
- And here in this corner,
the man in the silver mask is,
Samson, the champion.
- This is what would happen
if Don King took over opera.
(crowd chanting and whistling)
- Hey, I didn't ask to see that.
Okay, later.
- I'll take your coat and
put it in the rest room.
- Oh yes, the sport John Ravie
wrote about so eloquently.
- Well you know, before
he became a fallen angel,
Satan was a jock.
- This is very much
like the quiet man,
except the Mexicans in tights
know of him as the devil.
- Oh gee, time to get
really serious about this
(crowd chanting)
- Uh oh!
That's gotta be Forrester.
- Oh Mike, I can't
find Frank anywhere.
He never stays out this late,
what with his fear of halogen.
I've checked everywhere, the DQ,
the sewage treatment plant,
all his usual hangouts, nothing!
I'm just terribly
afraid that he's gone
and he's never coming back.
And if I cared one iota,
I would be devastated.
If I cared.
- Boy the boss is always
the last to know, huh?
Well, you see sir,
our time here on earth
is but a passing thing.
- He was assumed
by the angel Togo,
in a glorious coronation.
- Well it was kind
of a cosmic Togo.
You see his mission as
a second banana was...
And you were kinda
mean, so they--
- Well, there was
a fortune cookie
which foretold something
about something,
and then, well Gabby
Hayes is heavily involved.
- Anyway, he's not coming back.
- Sorry!
- Wait!
I can't imagine, I shan't.
Because it isn't true.
But it is.
Oh, this sucks.
Who'll be my guineapig
for my gene splicing,
my fingernail
transplants, my fajita.
Who will I blame my mistakes on?
Who will I kill?
♪ I've destroyed
and I've maimed ♪
♪ And I've kicked him ♪
♪ Now I'm a bully ♪
♪ With no victim ♪
♪ No adrenalin, thrill ♪
♪ Nor screams that I shrill ♪
♪ Who ♪
♪ Who will I kill ♪
♪ I crashed his
head a few times ♪
♪ Memories like nursery rhymes ♪
♪ No one died like
my TV's Frank ♪
♪ No sweet blood
could he spill ♪
♪ No cute tummy to drill ♪
♪ Who ♪
♪ Who will I kill ♪
♪ When I look upon the
first evening star ♪
♪ I remember when I
hooked his liver ♪
♪ To the engine of my car ♪
♪ I could tickle my aunt Liv ♪
♪ Give my dog a cyanide pill ♪
♪ But what Frank shaped void ♪
♪ Could they possible fill ♪
♪ Here's my money,
you can bank it ♪
♪ I'm no good without my Frank ♪
♪ It seems he could die ♪
♪ Without batting an eye ♪
♪ Now it seems I must
take my own bitter pill ♪
♪ Tell me who ♪
♪ Who will I kill ♪
- Goodbye Frank!
And remember, wherever you are
I will kill you.
- In a sick way, I feel touched.
We'll be right back.
(upbeat music)
- What's the matter with him?
I swear he's trying to kill ya.
- Nice way with the song.
- That fellow's
not the black mask.
He's been using karate on me,
and he could kill
me with one blow.
- Listen, I'll ask that they
suspend the match Samson.
- No, I'm gonna see this
thing through to the end.
- But you're crazy, he's
trying to murder you.
- I'd already been warned
about this, but we'll see.
- Can I lose the mask, its hot.
- Oh good, give
me more wrestling.
- I bet the whole place
smells like Bree by now.
- So much for my
fresh new start.
- Oh, and the devil
is out of the ring,
the prince of darkness
has fallen on a woman
in the front row.
- It wasn't such a good idea
to send a killer
vampire into the crowd.
- Oh there you are.
This mask makes it so hard
to know who know who
you should wrestle.
- This isn't strictly
wrestling, isn't it?
- No!
- Um, ouch!
- Let's see, is
this melon fresh?
- And the crowd goes wild.
(Crow and Servo boo)
I just think the audience
could have been singing
hayalaya and cock fighting.
- Huh, Luis!
You'd almost think that
was all planned out.
- Samson trained by watching
road runner cartoons.
- Here, that wasn't working,
let me try that, there we go.
- Oh, they resort to
second grade tactics.
- The international, fight
like a girl championships.
- I've engaged in a
bit of pugilism myself.
- Well a face appeal is
ready to come off now.
- Hey, come on man,
don't ruin my gimmick.
- Don't touch mask!
- Wow, chicken wings.
- There's a zipper in back!
- That's gonna be Peter Lopes.
- That's part of the
face, it doesn't come off.
- It's an Oakridge boy!
- What, what?
It's my butt crack, isn't it?
- Pam, Texas Ranger.
- Call the pound.
You stay, you sit, ow.
- (mumbles) is
attacking the city.
Run, it's Fitzpatrick.
- Oh, now you're
just provoking him.
This is Howard Cosell,
how can this be considered
a legitimate sport?
- Okay, no more shape
shifters in the ring.
- Terrific floor show, hey?
- Look, it's very late Inspector
and I'm starting to get tired.
So, what's the use of waiting?
- Just a while longer,
until daylight.
It's safer, believe me.
- We'll get our
menus eventually.
(soft music)
- Ladies and
gentlemen, the Judds,
♪ Sister, sisters ♪
♪ Never were there
such devoted sisters ♪
- Which twin has the toning?
- Our wives don't understand us.
- Hello ladies!
Your special today is
a cheesy taco loco.
I'll be back to take
your order later.
- She's looking at me.
- Hey, she's looking at me.
- Okay then, let's
get a bloody Mary,
two straws, a blood sausage
and some blooded pudding.
- There is the girl
chosen as your successor.
Look at her!
- She looks exactly
like her ancestor.
She'll be worthy of my throne.
- But I hate her outfit.
- Oh God, those bitchy vampires
Debbie and Jennifer are here.
- She's been stuckod.
- My skin cleared up.
- Lillian Helmund on a bad day.
- Ah, Inspector,
watch the reflections,
those two in the rear there.
- They're checking me out.
- Huh, he knows we're ugly.
- I got a dine and
dash on table four.
(loud whistle shrills)
- No running by the pool.
- Arrest those two women.
- Any two women.
(loud whistle shrills)
- This couple needs a cab.
- The food here is terrible.
- And the portions so small.
- Did you see two
women come out?
They must be around here.
Surround the whole area.
I wanna search
thoroughly, understand?
- We just came for dinner.
- You two stay here with us.
We have to give this
young lady protection.
And keep your eyes open.
- Where devils go,
trouble follows.
- It's time I went to wait
back at the crypt Tundra,
if you fail again, you know
what there is in store for you.
- You have to give
me a pedicure.
- Well, we're pretty
safe here, hey?
- No danger here.
That's a cool Fang
Fanny car, neat.
- I think it would be better
if you went back to
the house with Diana.
I'll be waiting here.
My men will go along with you.
- It's the vampire
version of Goodfellas!
- Oh real mature
vampires, you big bullies.
- I don't need a
ride, thank you!
- You just tell 'em
Tony the big bad vampire
wants his money.
- Hey, I had this cab.
- Hey, look sir I
don't go to Hades
and if I do, it's
only during the day.
- These vampires
specialize in rough housing
and the black arts.
- The key stone vampires.
- Come here you
mortal son of a bitch.
- Turns out it's not Samson,
it's just a very flamboyant CPA.
- Circus of the
network vampires.
- Oh, jeez, I thought I
was done for the evening.
- Getting too old
for these raves.
- Gimme back my inhaler.
- The flying Nosforatu brothers.
- Samson, party of one,
your table is ready.
- The ultimate battle between
good and evil is really goofy.
- I didn't fork over the money
for the bat chasing
option on this car
and now I need it.
- Well, apparently
considerable taxiing
is necessary for
vampires to lift off.
- Okay, up up and oh jeez!
- Death race Liberaci.
- Our lady of Fatuma is
back and she is pissed.
- Why couldn't I have
been a vampire in Israel?
- It's a sign that says,
wild drug, 10000 miles.
- Edges light quickly.
- Oh please.
Hell, I'll just mark it
in my book as a kill.
- Can I get you a
glass of water or...
(upbeat music)
- There's no time
to lose Professor.
I'm trying to save Diana
and it depends on this code.
- Well, just as soon as
I finish this jumble.
- There, I really
read him the riot act.
- I like you, do you like me.
- A!
B!
- C, D!
- And here I think...
- Therefore I am.
- At last I've
got it, thank God.
- I've discovered the letter D.
Let me start the gelato
machine, oh good!
- Uh, sir we should probably
get to rescuing your daughter.
- John Forsythe in
bachelor father.
- Professor Rollof here,
I'm calling you Samson.
This is Professor Rollof,
come in, can you hear?
It's very important Samson,
emergency, please answer.
- I'm listening
Professor Rollof, this
is Samson answering.
Come in Professor, over.
- Listen Samson, the
crypt where you'll find
the vampires hiding,
is located in the
forest of White Pines.
So please hurry, I
think we may save Diana.
In a second we'll
be on our way there,
and I wish you good luck.
- Yeah good, whatever.
Look, I got a fare right now.
- Meanwhile in Little
Sheep, Wisconsin...
(spooky haunting music)
- Sometimes when
the moon is full,
Samson likes to turn
off the headlights
and just drive.
- Maybe if Cortes had
never conquered Moctezuma,
we would not have had
to watch this movie.
- Yeah!
♪ Go, el santo ♪
♪ Go el santo ♪
♪ Go el santo go ♪
- They move the
action to the den.
♪ See the Mexico
in your Chevrolet ♪
- Oh, thank goodness
a wrestle stop.
- If a wrestler
falls in the forest
and there's no one to hear it,
does it count as a fall?
- Oh, suddenly he
forgot how to drive.
- How come I haven't
noticed that before.
(loud screams)
- Ah come on,
everybody is doing it.
- Jeez, we haven't even
put the needle in yet.
(loud screams)
- Peter Garrett stars
in a very special ER.
- Please leave me alone.
- Do we honestly need another
remake of Little Women?
- Tundra, in a few short
minutes we will see the dawn.
You must hurry now.
- Oh, another hard
home for sale.
- Wow, man, this place is
like my first apartment
before I got my big
wrestling contract.
- I like what they've done
with the cobwebs in bat guano.
- Grapes, what good is being
the ruler of the underworld
if you gotta live
in a dump like this?
(owl hoots loudly)
♪ Who are you ♪
- Rebeca, what the
hell is Rebeca?
- It's a costume okay?
- Your very own, glow
in the dark Samson.
- Come on, do
something, wrestle even.
(loud screams)
- Tell me I didn't hear that.
- Hey buddy, take it
from a wise old me,
don't go in there.
- The only problem
with the mask is that,
it's really cutting off
the circulation by now.
- (laughs) nothing.
- Oh, it's a cage match.
- Please, do not
feed the Samson.
- Oh God, I never
wanted to see this.
- Hey, hey wrestling!
- He's got a full acre of area.
- Vampires have a
pretty basic agenda
with everyone they capture.
- Tell your sister Tundra,
that it's late, she must hurry.
- Tundra, mom says you're late.
- Touchdowns!
- I forgot to put up
the storm windows.
- At last we're going to know
who our stubborn enemy is.
Take off his mask.
- Oh I hope it
isn't Dalo Mladen!
- They're frightening.
- Oh wow, they must be ugly.
- Had they just
brought curtains,
it could have saved
the whole vampire race.
- But some people burn
easily in the sun.
- Hey, you wanna untie
me quick before you die.
- So how's your slab, huh?
- Oh yeah, rescue you and oh...
- Okay, but this is
the last time you guys.
- Well no one can
resist a good mix it up.
- Can I get a bendy straw?
- Oh, what was I doing before?
Oh yeah!
- Okay, bye then.
- Well see, it's 'cause they
didn't reapply their sunscreen
after sweating.
- Movie tone news,
presents the march of time.
- Oh damn, Martha
Graham dancers.
(loud shrill)
- Oh damn, all the
biffies are full.
- Panty raid (laughs)
I'm kidding of course.
Just gonna burn you to death.
I hope this is the
right thing to do.
- Well, I'll just
let God sort 'em out.
- That's always nice
Samson, just torch everyone.
- He's bested at every turn
and now you've got
a chance to light
some helpless women on fire.
(loud screams)
- Well, I think
that's about everyone.
I'm out of here.
- Authorities suspect arson.
- Hi honey, gee it's great
to be back at the castle.
Hope your sisters' dress up
Halloween slumber
party went well--
Oh my God!
- It's a clown car.
- You can put me
down, I can walk.
You don't have to...
- There's a live body Samson,
we've got some
questions to ask you.
- I decided not
to burn this one.
- Honey, I hate
to tell you this,
but an android from the future
is going to come and kill
you so you won't give birth.
- A thundering tire,
a flashing turn signal
and a heidi hi ho silver!
- Goodbye sweet
wrestling friend.
- Huh, God bless Samson.
- Who is he Papa?
- God, well he's a
Judeo-Christian deity.
- I don't think
you'll ever know.
But I'll say this my dear
- He's a fruitcake!
- In this age where there
are certain evil men
who propose to destroy us,
Samson is an example
to men of goodwill
who serve justice.
- Well, I do what I can.
I gotta go rinse
out a few things.
(gentle music)
- What a dope!
- Well guys, Frank is gone
and maybe now will be good time
to read our letters to
him, okay Tom Servo?
- Okay let's see.
Dear Frank, well I
guess I better be going,
yours truly Servo.
- Kinda short!
- Well, that's nice.
Crow, how about you, do
you have a nice letter?
- Dear Frank, you
are a pig, love Crow?
(laughter)
- Come on you guys.
Now you're making fun of a guy
who's been very nice to us.
I mean, sure Frank's dumb,
but we could have
had it a lot worse.
I bet Gypsy's letter
is more appropriate.
- Yeah thanks Mike.
Dear Frank, I'm glad that
you are in a better place.
Forrester is evil,
and you have been a
welcome touch of kindness.
Others may put you down,
but I will always say,
give me my TV's Frank,
and when he shall die
cut him into tiny stars
and he shall make the
face of heaven so fine,
that all the world will
fall in love with the night
and pay no heed to
the garish sun, amen!
- That was beautiful!
Not as poetic as Dear
Frank you're a pig,
but still, it, what?
♪ Maybe Frank about Frank ♪
♪ 'cause Frank is ♪
Frank!
It really is you.
Speak to me Frank, speak to me.
- Clay, close your robe.
- Sorry!
- Oh, I just
thought I'd check in
from the ethereal outer world,
and see how you're doing.
- Frank, I can't
believe I won't be able
to kill you anymore.
- Don't worry Clay!
Because somewhere
deep inside your soul,
you'll always be killing me.
And remember this my
sentimental friend.
Even though I will
forever be in your heart
till the end of your days,
you'll be a
profoundly, lonely man.
- Thank you Frank,
that's very kind of you.
- And just let me say
this to anyone out there,
who's working for
an abusive boss.
Do not despair!
Never let him crush your spirit,
even if he's already
crushed your skull.
Always be yourself, and
wave your freak flag high.
- Jeez, it must be horrible
to work for a boss like that.
Frank, could I ask you
one thing before you go?
- Sure!
Could you push the button Frank?
- (laughs) watch me rock.
(gentle music)
- Chief I saw two
corpses in the garden.